Guide to the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs, 1840-present CTC.1966.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs
1840-present
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Curtis, Ford E.
Curtis, Harriet R.
CTC.1966.01
84 Linear Feet (mss boxes)
The Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection contains tens of thousands of Pittsburgh theatre programs from the 1840s to the present. They include productions from current performing arts groups in Pittsburgh. Sometimes newspaper clippings, marketing materials, photographs, and memorabilia related to the theatres and performing arts companies are stored with the programs.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
History
One of the main components of the Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection is its Pittsburgh theatre programs. Dr. Ford E. Curtis began teaching drama in the English department at the University of Pittsburgh in 1924. He and his wife, Harriet, were avid theatre goers, attending performances every week. After his retirement in 1961, he began to add to their personal collection of playbills and programs in the hopes of building a collection to donate to Pitt.
In the early 1960s, Dr. Curtis even went so far as to put advertisements in Carnegie Magazine, the Western Pennsylvania Historical Magazine, and programs for the Pittsburgh Playhouse. The advertisements put out a call for any and all Pittsburgh programs to be donated to him; he even listed his home address and telephone number, with the goal to build a Pittsburgh theatre history collection for the University of Pittsburgh. Large numbers of programs were also donated by the New York Public Library and the Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh.
The materials that Dr. Curtis amassed -- his own collection, materials donated to him, and the Curtis Collection staff's current efforts to acquire additional programs -- help to document the history of theatre and the performing arts in Pittsburgh.
Accruals
Donations are added to the collection annually. These donations come from the producing groups themselves and the general public. If you are interested in donating theatre programs to the collection, please contact Archives & Special Collections staff.
Scope and Content Notes
Individual programs in the collection are mostly organized by the theatre or venue where the production took place. These venues are arranged alphabetically by name, then chronologically. In some instances, a performing arts group did not have a home theatre or consistent venue where they performed, such as the Civic Light Opera and the Quantum Theatre. In these instances, the programs and other materials are filed under the title of the performing arts group.
With each series, the total number of document boxes is listed. The boxes are not numbered consecutively as found in other archival collections because these numbers regularly change with new donations. Typically, the collection's policy is to only keep two copies of a program, although exceptions to this include commemorative programs and programs that are autographed or contain marginalia.
Where individual programs are listed for online access, the date listed is usually the start date for the production's engagement. Typically, productions would start on a Monday and the same program would be issued throughout the run of performances.
Please note that this collection does not represent all of the Pittsburgh theatre programs in the Curtis Collection. Many of the Pittsburgh programs prior to 1930 are in our scrapbook collection. Please consult the Special Collections staff with inquiries for theatres that you cannot locate in this collection guide.
Previous Citation
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Theatre Programs, 1840-present, CTC.1966.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh
Arrangement
The series of this collection are arranged alphabetically by the title of the venue or performing arts group.
Related Materials
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Information Files, 1879-present, CTC.Infofiles.Pgh, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Ford E. and Harriet R. Curtis Theatre Collection of Pittsburgh Performing Arts Photographs, 1907-present, CTC.1966.03, Curtis Theatre Collection,Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Clippings (Information artifacts); Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Theater programs; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh Public Theater; Pittsburgh Playhouse; Bucks County Playhouse (New Hope, Pa.); Civic Light Opera of Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh Savoyards; Iron Clad Agreement (Theatrical company); 99¢ Floating Theatre; Nixon Theatre (Organization: Pittsburgh, Pa.); Walnut Street Theatre (Organization: Philadelphia, Pa.); Chatham College; White Barn Theatre (North Huntingdon, Pa.); Pittsburgh Cultural Trust; Carnegie-Mellon Theatre Company
- 19th Century Pittsburgh Theatres, 1840-1935; I.; 2 boxes
  - Academy of Music, 1868-1899; 1.
    Scope and Content Notes
    Other names for this venue: Harry Williams' Academy of Music.
    - Advertising - Interesting Religious Service, January 12, 1868; 1.
    - Program - Henry Nicholls' Recitals from Memory, December 17, 1868; 2.
    - Ticket - Mercantile Library Lectures, Henry Nicholls, December 18, 1868; 3.
    - Ticket - Mercantile Library Lectures, John B. Gough, January 16, 1869; 4.
    - Advertising - Mercantile Library Lectures, A Struggle for Life, January 25, 1869; 5.
    - Advertising - Mercantile Library Lectures, Mrs. Scott-Siddons At the Academy of Music, February 8, 1869; 6.
    - Program - Mercantile Library Lectures, Dramtic Readings with Mary Frances Scott-Siddons, February 8, 1869; 7.
    - Program - Mercantile Library Lectures, Dramatic Readings with Mary Frances Scott-Siddons, February 11, 1869; 8.
    - Opera program - The Daughter of the Regiment, October 28, 1871; 9.
    - Burlesque program - Rentz-Santley Novelty & Burlesque Company; Manchester & Jennings; the Etzeltine Sisters; and Miss Minnie Farrell, October 3, 1881; 10.
  - Alvin Theatre, 1893-1935; 2.; 1 box
    - Theatre program - Fedora with Sarah Bernhardt, March 23, 1892; 1.
    - Theatre program - Rip Van Winkle; Cricket on the Hearth; and Lend Me Five Shillings with Joseph Jefferson, November 9, 1896; 2.
    - Theatre program - L'Aiglon with Maude Adams, February 11, 1901; 3.
    - Theatre program - If I Were King and Hamlet with E.H. Sothern, December 15, 1902; 4.
    - Theatre program - H.M.S. Pinafore or The Lass That Loved a Sailor benefit perfomances for the Industrial Home for Crippled Children; the Juvenile Court Association of Allegheny County; and the Tuberculosis League of Pittsburgh, June 1, 1909; 5.
  - Casino Musee, 3.
    - Theatre program - Maurithus & Martinnette Bros. Pantomine Little Bo Peep; John Mayon; and Rodgers & Owens' Shadowgraphs!, 1.
  - Duquesne Theatre, 1890-1919; 4.; 1 box
    - Theatre program - Herrmann the Great performance, April 10, 1893; 1.
    - Theatre program - L'Enfant Prodigue, October 9, 1893; 2.
  - Exposition Park, 1885; 5.
    - Concert program - Mexican National Band, August 10, 1885; 1.
  - Fifteenth Ward School Hall, 1875; 6.
    - Theatre program - The Spectre Bridgroom or, A Ghost in Spite of Himself!; and Waddy, The Fat Boy!, May 29, 1875; 1.
  - Klopfer's Hall, 1875-1878; 7.
    Klopfer's Hall was on the corner of Butler and 43rd Street.
    - Theatre program - Little Barefoot! with Miss Annie Zern, 1.
    - Ticket - Little Barefoot!, 2.
    - Theatre program - All for Her!; and Nan, the Good for Nothing with Miss Annie Zern, 3.
    - Advertising - Family Jars!; Too Attentive by Half!; Naval Engagements!; and Loan of a Lover!, October 23, 1875; 4.
    - Theatre program - Waddy, the Fat Boy!; Idiot Witness!, December 4, 1875; 5.
    - Advertising - Everybody's Friend!; and Michael Erie!, December 24, 1875; 6.
    - Advertising - Readings and Character Recitations!; and The Bruised Tragedian!, 1878; 7.
    - Program - Readings and Character Recitations!; and The Bruised Tragedian!, May 9, 1878; 8.
  - Library Hall, 1871-1899; 8.
    Other names for this venue: the Mercantile Library Hall, Chalet Bijou Theatre, Bijou Theatre, the Lyceum, the Academy, and the Lyceum.
    - Mercantile Library Hall, 1871-1875
      - Concert program - Theodore Thomas' Orchestra with Miss Anna Mehlig, March 3, 1871; 1.
      - Advertising - Henry VIII with Charlotte Cushman; and Miscellaneous Selections, April 1, 1872; 2.
      - Opera program - Il Trovatore with Clara Louise Kellogg and the Kellogg Grand English Opera, December 3, 1874; 3.
      - Opera program - La Grande Duchesse with Marie Aimee and the French Opera Bouffe Company, December 8, 1874; 4.
      - Opera program - Bohemian Girl! by the Gounod Club, December 17, 1874; 5.
      - Theatre program - Musette or, The Secret of Guilde Court with Lotta, February 18, 1875; 6.
      - Opera program - Madame L'archiduc! with Miss Emily Soldene, February 24, 1875; 7.
      - Program - Charlotte Cushman's Farewell, April 2, 1875; 8.
      - Vaudeville program - "Carncross & Dixey's Minstrels!" Stage Struck!; etc, April 16, 1875; 9.
      - Theatre program - The Cricket on the Hearth!; and That Blessed Baby! with Mr. J. L. Toole, April 27, 1875; 10.
      - Theatre program - Off the Line!; Old Friends!; and Ici on Prale Francais! with Mr. J. L. Toole, April 30, 1875; 11.
      - Theatre program - Masks and Faces! or, Before and Behind the Curtain with Laura Keene, May 1, 1875; 12.
      - Theatre program - Morning Call; The Soldier's Daughter with Laura Keene, May 2, 1875; 13.
      - Vaudeville program - Tony Pastor's Troupe in The Fisherman!; Black Troubadours; and Nervous Dutchman!, May 19, 1875; 14.
      - Opera program - Grand Duchess by J.F. Zimmerman's Mexican Juvenile Opera Troupe, October 21, 1875; 15.
      - Theatre program - Jane Eyre with Miss Charlotte Thompson and Mr. W. E. Sheridan, December 1, 1875; 16.
      - Opera program - The Hugeunots!, December 7, 1875; 17.
    - Library Hall, 1876-1886
      - Concert program - With Theresa Titiens; Arabella Goddard; Inez Kennedy; Baccei; Orlandini; and Mark Keiser, January 3, 1876; 1.
      - Theatre program - Humpty Dumpty with James S. Maffitt, February 5, 1876; 2.
      - Theatre broadside - Bartley Campbell's Old Dusquesne!, April 21, 1876; 3.
      - Theatre program - Richelieu! with Mr. Charles Pope, October 6, 1876; 4.
      - Theatre program - Maud Muller with Miss Genevieve Rogers, October 10, 1876; 6.
      - Theatre program - Henry VIII with Miss Augusta Dargon, November 1, 1876; 5.
      - Theatre program - Two Can Play at That Game; and The Brook!, December 9, 1876; 7.
      - Theatre program - Macbeth! with Janauschek, December 16, 1876; 8.
      - Theatre program - Forbidden Fruit!, January 16, 1877; 9.
      - Theatre program - Richelieu! or The Conspiracy with Lawrence Barrett, March 5, 1877; 10.
      - Theatre program - Poulet and Poulette with Miss Emily Soldene, Mr. Knight Aston, and Miss Rose Stella, March 14, 1877; 11.
      - Theatre program - La Fille De Madame Angot with Miss Emily Soldene, March 17, 1877; 12.
      - Theatre program - Pink Dominos! with Chas. F. Coghlan and Agnes Booth, October 19, 1877; 13.
      - Opera Program - Mignon with C. L. Kellogg, Marie Roze, and A. L. Federico, January 29, 1878; 14.
      - Theatre program - East Lynne, March 20, 1878; 15.
      - Theatre program - Doyle Brothers with Edward Harrigan and Tony Hart, May 1878; 16.
      - Concert program - The Kate Thayer Grand Concert Co., November 18, 1879; 17.
      - Burlesque program - Carncross' Minstrels; Henry Moses' Shadboat Pinafore!; etc, April 28, 1879; 18.
      - Concert program - Grand Testimonial Concert to Mr. J. T. Irwin, May 27, 1880; 19.
      - Theatre program - Arrah-Na-Pogue, or the Wicklaw Wedding with Agnes Robertson, September 27, 1880; 20.
      - Opera program - Strakosch & Hess Englsh Opera Co. in Mefistofele! and Carmen!, February 14, 1881; 21.
      - Theatre program - Belles of the Kitchen; Cousin Joe with the Vokes Family, October 17, 1881; 22.
      - Opera program - Wilbur Opera Company in The Mascot, November 21, 1881; 23.
      - Theatre program - The Professor! with W.H. Gillette, January 30, 1882; 24.
      - Theatre program - Much Ado About Nothing with Hortense Rhéa, February 11, 1882; 25.
      - Opera program - Corman Church Choir Co. in Patience or, Bunthrone's Bride, February 17, 1882; 26.
      - Theatre program - Photos with Alice Harrison and Louis Harrison, February 20, 1882; 27.
      - Vaudeville program - Carncross' Minstrels in Life Behind the Scenes or, the Black Lily's Debut; Cogill Brothers; Fred Dart; etc, May 14, 1882; 28.
      - Opera program - Boston Ideal Opera Company in Bohemian Girl, January 28, 1883; 29.
      - Theatre program - As You Like It with Margaret Mather, November 19, 1883; 30.
      - Advertising - Madison Square Theatre in Esmeralda, December 3, 1883; 31.
      - Concert program - Grand Music Festival, March 11-14, 1884; 32.
      - Opera program - Fay Templeton Opera Company in Girofle-Girofla, June 2, 1884; 33.
      - Vaudeville program - Haverly's Genuine Colored Minstrels; Alex Hunter; the Canebrake Spectres; etc, November 15, 1884; 34.
      - Opera program - The Boston Ideal Opera Company in Fanchonette, January 20, 1885; 35.
      - Theatre program - Madison Square Theatre in May Blossom, the Fisherman's Daughter, February 23, 1885; 36.
      - Opera program - The Ford English Opera Company in Martha with Zelda Seguin, April 1, 1885; 37.
      - Opera program - The Emma Abbott Grand Opera Company in Rigoletto, April 14, 1885; 38.
      - Opera program - The Emma Abbott Grand Opera Company in Semiramide, April 17, 1885; 39.
      - Opera program - The Emma Abbott Grand Opera Company in Il Trovatore, April 18, 1885; 40.
      - Theatre program - Pittsburgh Press Club Testimonial featuring Musette, or the Secret of Guilde Court with Lotta Crabtree; Sheehan and Coyne; Sea of Ice with Lottie Church; etc., April 23, 1885; 41.
      - Opera program - The Boston Ideal Opera Company in Martha, May 19, 1885; 42.
      - Opera program - The Boston Ideal Opera Company in The Musketeers, May 20, 1885; 43.
      - Opera program - The Boston Ideal Opera Company in Giralda, May 21, 1885; 44.
      - Burlesque program - Pinafore in Pennsylvania Dutch, June 8, 1885; 45.
      - Opera program - The McCaull Opera Comique Company in The Black Hussar, October 5, 1885; 46.
      - Opera program - New York Thalia Grand and Comic Company in Nanon, or the Hostess of the Golden Lamb, December 7, 1885; 47.
      - Opera program - New York Thalia Grand and Comic Company in Postillon von Lonjumeau, December 12, 1885; 48.
      - Opera program - The Boston Ideal Opera Company in The Musketeers, December 25, 1885; 49.
      - Advertising - Alexander Salvini tour, Dcember 31, 1885; 50.
      - Theatre program - The Duke's Motto with Alexander Salvini and Viola Allen, January 2, 1886; 51.
      - Opera program - The Emma Abbott Grand Opera Company in Faust, March 26, 1886; 52.
      - Theatre program - Camille with Helena Modjeska, April 17, 1886; 53.
    - Chalet Bijou Theatre, 1886-1887
      - Theatre program - Thompson Opera Company in The Mikado, September 13, 1886; 1.
      - Theatre program - Nordeck and The Three Guardsmen with Frank Mayo, September 20, 1886; 2.
      - Theatre program - The Humming Bird with Nate Salsbury and Nillie McHenry, December 27, 1886; 3.
      - Theatre program - My Partner with Louis Aldrich, February 14, 1887; 4.
      - Theatre program - Theodora with Lillian Olcott, March 21,1887; 5.
      - Opera program - Emma Abbott Grand English Opera Company in Lucretia Borgia; The Mikado; Bohemian Girl; Il Travatore; Crispino; Linda of Chamouni; Mignon; Chimes of Normandy, April 25, 1887; 6.
      - Theatre program - Camille with Clara Morris and Henry Miller, May 2, 1887; 7.
    - Bijou, 1887-1899
      - Theatre program - Our Angel with Lizzie Evans for the grand opening of the Bijou Theatre, September 5, 1887; 1.
      - Theatre program - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde with Richard Mansfield, November 7, 1887; 2.
      - Advertising - Annie Pixley in a magnificent repertoire, November 24, 1887; 3.
      - Theatre program - The Honeymoon with Margaret Mather, February 13, 1888; 4.
      - Theatre program - She, April 2, 1888; 5.
      - Theatre program - The Jilt with Dion Boucicault, May 14, 1888; 6.
      - Theatre program - The Shaughraun with Dion Boucicault, May 14, 1888; 7.
      - Theatre program - Tin Soldier, November 19, 1888; 8.
      - Theatre program - Erminie, February 18, 1889; 9.
      - Theatre program - The White Slave, October 2, 1893; 10.
      - Theatre program - The Corsican Brothers with Robert B. Mantell, May 15, 1899; 11.
      - Theatre program - The Dagger and the Cross with Robert B. Mantell, September 11, 1899; 12.
  - New Opera House, 1866-1870
  - Odd Fellows' Hall, 1869-1897; 9.
    Other names for this venue: Foster's National, the Apollo, the National, Opera House, Fifth Avenue Opera House, Fifth Avenue Lyceum, Harris Mammoth Museum, the Harris, and the Avenue Theatre.
    - Opera House, 1869-1870
      - Theatre program - Rip Van Winkle with Mr. Joseph Jefferson, March 16, 1869; 1.
      - Theatre Program - King Lear with Edwin Booth, November 25, 1870; 2.
      - Theatre Program - Little Nell and the Marchioness! with Lotta Crabtree, December 23, 1870; 3.
    - Fifth Avenue Lyceum, 1880; 8.
      - Concert program - Grand Concert of Scottish Songs, by Hamilton Corbett, April 19, 1880; 1.
    - Harris' Mammoth Museum, 1884-1886
      - Vaudeville program - Yankee in Love; B. and B. with Maggie Willet and Harry Thorne; etc, March 10, 1884; 1.
      - Theatre program - Fanchon, The Cricket with Cora Van Tassel, February 23, 1885; 2.
      - Theatre program - Matlack Combination in A Celebrated Case!, March 30, 1885; 3.
      - Theatre program - Fun on the Bristol with E.D. Tannehill's Comedy Company and Miss St. George Hussey, September 21, 1885; 4.
      - Theatre program - Bandmann-Beaudet Comapny in The Hunchback; The Merchant of Venice, Romeo and Juliet, and Othello, December 28, 1885; 5.
      - Advertising - Davy Crocket with Edwin F. Mayo, September 6, 1886; 6.
      - Vaudeville program - Prof. E.M. Worth lecture; Hick's and Sawyer's Consolidated Colored Minstrels, September 13, 1886; 7.
      - Vaudeville program - Prof. Tony White's London Punch and Judy; Prof. E.M. Worth lecture; Silver Spur!, September 27, 1886; 8.
    - Harris' Theatre, 1888; 9.
      - Theatre program - Pat's Wardrobe with Pat Rooney, February 20, 1888; 9.
    - Avenue Theatre, 1897
      - Vaudeville program - The Lottery of Love; Morris' Famous Pony Circus; etc, January 25, 1897; 2.
      - Vaudeville program - The Private Secretary; Zinematographie; etc, March 15, 1897; 3.
      - Vaudeville program - Rosedale with Mr. Joseph Haworth; Jane Whitbeck; Centure Bros.; etc, June 14, 1897; 4.
      - Vaudeville program - An Old Love Story with Auguste Van Biene and Miss Lena Burnleigh; the American Biograph owned and operated by the American Mutoscope Co.; etc, November 29, 1897; 5.
  - Pittsburgh Opera House, 1871-1916; 10.
    Located on Diamond Street (now Forbes Avenue) the Pittsburgh Opera House opened January 30th, 1871. On September 19th, 1887 the theatre was renamed the Grand Opera House.
    - Pittsburgh Opera House
      - Theatre program - Wild Oats!; and Blackened Susan with Edwin Adams, September 26, 1874; 1.
      - Theatre program - Clancarity! or, Wedded and Wooed with Edwin Adams, October 2, 1874; 2.
      - Theatre program - Lady of Lyons with Katherine Randolph, October 7, 1874; 3.
      - Theatre program - London Assurance! with Jane Coombs, November 5, 1874; 4.
      - Theatre program - Money! with Lawrence Barrett, November 17, 1874; 5.
      - Theatre program - Julius Caesar with Lawrence Barrett, November 18, 1874; 6.
      - Theatre program - Hunchback with Clara Morris, December 7, 1874; 7.
      - Theatre program - Rip Van Winkle, or, The Sleep of Twenty Years with Joseph Jefferson, December 16, 1874; 8.
      - Theatre program - The Heir at Law; and Toodles with J. S. Clarke, December 28, 1874; 9.
      - Theatre program - King John! with Agnes Booth and J. B. Booth, January 16, 1875; 10.
      - Theatre program - 'Twixt Axe and Crown with Clara Rousby, February 15, 1875; 11.
      - Theatre program - Col. Mulberry Sellers! with John T. Raymond, April 14, 1875; 12.
      - Theatre program - Salsbury's Troubadours in Little Mother; and Patchwork!, June 12, 1875; 13.
      - Burlesque program - Bryant's Minstrels in Soiree d'Ethiope! and Dark Deeds in Dixey!; Walters and Morton; etc., June 22, 1875; 14.
      - Theatre program - Augustin Daly's Fifth Avenue Theatre Company in Big Bonanza!, September 29, 1875; 15.
      - Theatre program - Furbish's Fifth Avenue Combination in Two Orphans, October 26, 1875; 16.
      - Theatre program - Richelieu! or, The Conspiracy with Barry Sullivan, November 8, 1875; 17.
      - Theatre program - Richard III with Barry Sullivan, November 9, 1875; 18.
      - Opera program - La Jolie Parfumeuse! with Alice Oates, December 2, 1875; 19.
      - Opera program - Trial by Jury!; and Les Bavards with Alice Oates, December 4, 1875; 20.
      - Theatre program - Victor of Rhe! or, Risen from the Dead with J. Newton Gotthold, December 22, 1875; 21.
      - Theatre program - Twelve Temptations!, December 28, 1875; 22.
      - Theatre program - The Unequal Match! with Jane Coombs, January 15, 1876; 23.
      - Theatre program - Macbeth with Barry Sullivan, February 3, 1876; 24.
      - Theatre program - Hamlet with Barry Sullivan, February 4, 1876; 25.
      - Theatre program - Avalanche! or, Under the Snow with Effie E. Ellsler, February 22, 1876; 26.
      - Theatre program - As You Like It! or, The Forest of Arden with Effie E. Ellsler, February 26, 1876; 27.
      - Theatre program - Mighty Dollar! with William J. Florence and Malvina Florence, March 7, 1876; 28.
      - Theatre program - Musette with Lotta Crabtree, March 24, 1876; 29.
      - Theatre program - Guy Mannering! with Emma Waller, April 8, 1876; 30.
      - Theatre program - Dundreary Married and Settled! with E.A. Sothern, April 27, 1876; 31.
      - Theatre program - Our American Cousin! with E.A. Sothern, April 29, 1876; 32.
      - Theatre program - Galatea or, the Statue; and Leah, the Forsaken with Katherine Randolph, October 3, 1876; 33.
      - Theatre program - No Thoroughfare! with Charles Fechter and Lizzie Price, October 18, 1876; 34.
      - Theatre program - Monte Cristo with Charles Fechter and Lizzie Price, October 28, 1876; 35.
      - Theatre program - Our American Cousin! with E.A. Sothern, November 7, 1876; 36.
      - Theatre program - Hornet's Nest! and Dundreary Married & Settled! with E.A. Sothern, November 10, 1876; 37.
      - Theatre program - Romeo and Juliet with Adelaide Neilson and Eben Plympton, November 15, 1876; 38.
      - Theatre program - Everybodie's Friend with John E. Owens and Minnette Thompson, November 21, 1876; 39.
      - Theatre program - Conn In The Shaughraun with Dion Boucicault, February 15, 1877; 40.
      - Souvenir benefit program - Two Orphans with Kate Claxton, March 2, 1877; 41.
      - Opera program - Baba with Belle Howitt and William H. Fitzgerald, August 28, 1877; 42.
      - Theatre program - Victims!; and Solon Shingle! with John E. Owens, September 12, 1877; 43.
      - Theatre program - The Danites with McKee Rankin and Kitty Blanchard, January 9, 1878; 44.